export const mockQuestion: QuestionData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Question 1",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid1",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Question 2",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid2",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Question 3",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid3",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Question 4",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid4",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Question 5",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid5",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Question 6",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid6",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Question 7",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid7",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Question 8",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid8",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Question 9",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid9",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Question 10",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid10",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Question 11",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid11",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Question 12",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid12",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Question 13",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid13",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Question 14",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid14",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Question 15",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid15",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "Question 16",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid16",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "Question 17",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid17",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Question 18",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid18",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "Question 19",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid19",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Question 20",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid20",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "Question 21",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid21",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "Question 22",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid22",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "Question 23",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid23",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "Question 24",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid24",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Question 25",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid25",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "Question 26",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid26",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "Question 27",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid27",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "Question 28",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid28",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "Question 29",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid29",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "Question 30",
    choice: [
      { label: "Answer 1", value: "a" },
      { label: "Answer 2", value: "b" },
      { label: "Answer 3", value: "c" },
      { label: "Answer 4", value: "d" },
    ],
    relationAnswer: "uuid30",
  },
];

export const mockAnswer = [
  { id: "uuid1", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid2", answer: "b" },
  { id: "uuid3", answer: "c" },
  { id: "uuid4", answer: "d" },
  { id: "uuid5", answer: "b" },
  { id: "uuid6", answer: "c" },
  { id: "uuid7", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid8", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid9", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid10", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid11", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid12", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid13", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid14", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid15", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid16", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid17", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid18", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid19", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid20", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid21", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid22", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid23", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid24", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid25", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid26", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid27", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid28", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid29", answer: "a" },
  { id: "uuid30", answer: "a" },
];
